如果我们可以 现在我打算将
Now I'd like to work on breaking down
副总统公务上的
the vice president's official
以及政治上的职责分类
versus political duties if we can.
先生 我被告知我会被问及效率方面的问题
Sir, I was told that I'd be asked questions about efficiency.
目前为止你几乎没问过
So far you have barely asked me any.
你的效率听证会可不怎么有效率
Your efficiency hearing isn't very efficient.
你想要问题么?
You want a question? What can you tell me
关于Quantico海军基地的访问你能说些什么?
about this visit to the Marine base at Quantico?
政府让两个不同的车队去同一个地方
The government sending two different motorcades, the defense secretary's
一个是国防部长的 一个是副总统的
and the VP's, to the same location.
那看上去一点效率都没有 哦 他妈的狗屎
- That doesn't seem very efficient. - Oh, shit a shark.
这就是为什么我告诉她要装聋作哑
This is why I told her to be dull.